Ready.
>> Caleb Pros middle of the field. Love a
catch. Love a 20. Love a 10. Love. I am
Jeff.
>> Touchdown Bears. Mighty Manungi. Another
touchdown run.
>> What was it like playing for coach Dao?
>> I don't want to answer any questions
like that.
>> Kyro Santos is up. It's good. Bears win
it. No way.
>> Now, Bears, etc. Brought to you by
Miller Lightite with the voices of the
Bears, Jeff Joniac and Tom Fer.
>> From the NFL annual meeting at the
Arizona Billmore, it's Bears etc.
episode 215 with Super Bowl winning
Bears guard Tom Fer. I'm Jeff Jonia.
This episode of Bears etc. brought to
you by Miller Life, the official beer
partner of your Chicago Bears. Tastes
like Miller Time Chicago. Go to
millerlife.com/bearsspot
to find delivery options near you.
Celebrate responsibly. Miller Brewing
Company, Milwaukee, Wisconsin. 96
calories and 3.2 two carbs per 12
ounces. Coming up, our sit down with Ben
Johnson, the Bears head coach at the
meetings here. Uh Tom, yesterday you
heard the entire half hour uh
presentation from uh the media and the
questions about Ben and you could see
how excited and genuinely
uh intense he is already about this
upcoming season and what's in store for
these Bears. Well, just imagine what's
going through the mind of Ben Johnson
after year one being hired for the first
time head coach and the expectations of
a firsttime head coach in the charter
franchise in the NFL. And then you go on
to have player development, coaching
staff development and the success that
they had and some of the most exciting
moments of any football team in the
history of the league. Gosh Lee, how do
you follow that up? And so I don't think
Ben is putting any undue pressure on
himself. I think it's the same pressure
that he's always lived with as a person
and now as a head coach.
>> Tom, how would you characterize his uh
time on task uh really over the course
of the season and what do you anticipate
from a secondyear head coach? Um you've
really never experienced that in your
career, right? You had legends already
situated in their job for quite some
time in Mike Ditka and Don Schula. Uh,
of course maybe you experienced it in
college, but what's that year two do you
project going to look like with time on
task because everything he put in place
is already in place. So I would think
he's off to a great head start for 2026.
>> I I think it's two-tier. I think it's
going to be equally as challenging for
every one of his assistant coaches that
are employed by the Ben Johnson and the
Chicago Bears. the work hours that
they're expected to put in. And then the
development of individual players and
their position specifically. And then
when you look at it through a mind of a
player, it's going to be even more
competitive than it was last year. And I
think you have to understand of what is
going to be expected of you on an
everyday practice basis, the effort
that's going to be expected of you and
the end result. you're going to know
what it's like going into watch film
with the head coach and you watch film
with your position coaches. So, there's
a lot, you know, but it doesn't decrease
the expectations at all in terms of work
ethic and work effort. Tom, I want to
address the center position. I didn't do
that in the interview. I try to ask
different questions uh based on what the
media asked, but uh right out of the
gate yesterday uh a lot of discussion
about uh Drew Dolman and what he meant
and you know better than anybody what
that position means and maybe uh most of
us understated that position but when
his quote was he's a big reason we got
the plane off the ground was Drew
Dolman. Um, so he says no offense uh
will have success without that position
and selfishly they wanted him back. They
feel they've got a good option now and
Garrett Bradberry moving forward. But
when you heard that, did that make sense
to you?
>> 100%. Because there's a lot of different
disciplines that affect the center
position. First of all, you break the
huddle and you get up over the ball. You
have to have a good relationship uh
verbally and vocally with the
quarterback. You have to understand the
timing of his rhythm of the cadence. And
then you have to understand how to view
the defense in terms of the two plays
that are called in the huddle and what
you could possibly go to if the defense
isn't giving you what you expected. And
then with all those changes at the line
of scrimmage during the cadence, you
also got to be responsible for calling
out the linebacker of responsibility,
telling that if you're changing the play
from a run to a pass, what direction the
pass protection's going. So the center
isn't just break the huddle, snap the
ball. It's, you know, break the huddle
and then have like a 50 things go
through your mind. Make sure you're on
the same page as the other four
offensive linemen and the quarterback
and the specific timing of a football
play in regards to the cadence, but also
how that goes along with motion. There's
a lot of responsibility that falls on uh
the experience of the center position.
>> Well, in Bradberry, they feel they got a
a perfect fit. fit like a glove was the
expression and they leaned into Dan
Roshar and Kyle Dean the offensive line
coaches Tommy about their input on
Bradberry. Uh perfect in a wide zone
running game. Of course, Ben likes
multiple type, you know, he likes the
gap, he likes the right zone as well,
but and his pass protection he feels is
solid. So, I think this is a great first
step. They move quickly. I think Ryan
Ples uh should get a lot of credit as
well. his team of people went right to
the right to work on getting this thing
fixed immediately and underscoring the
importance of it in this Ben scheme. I
think they did a heck of a job. Tom, I
also want to bring up uh the void in
leadership right now that that it's a
vacuum that has to be filled. I'm
leaning on Caleb Williams to take
another step in that regard, but Ben
really really got a lot out of Kevin
Bard in that regard. Um h how do you
anticipate that looking to you down the
road here? uh especially on the
defensive side of the ball, but just
overall having a voice like Bard was
really instrumental.
>> Yeah, but that was Kevin Byard's first
year with Ben Johnson. This is Kobe
Bryant's first year with Ben Johnson.
And you know, coming in with the Dennis
Allen staff and his defensive
philosophy. So, I don't think I listen,
I admire Kevin Bard, what he brought
here. I have a tremendous amount of
respect for him and everything. I
watched him go about his business, but I
feel Kobe Bryant is up to those
expectations, but he's also confident in
his abilities. And so, yeah, you're
looking for that next man up mentality
and who is going to accept that
leadership role, but I think he's ready,
willing, and able to do that. And, um,
you still have some senior leadership in
the back end of the defense that can
help fill that void of Kevin Bard. But
um that's kind of the transition you go
through year in and year out in uh NFL
and career longevities.
>> Blue Moon made brighter and a proud
partner of the Chicago Bears. Celebrate
responsibly Chicago. And good news
Chicago United Airlines is getting brand
new planes with all the bells and
whistles like Bluetooth connectivity,
screens at every seat and room for
everyone's roller bag. United proud to
fly the Chicago Bears in YouTube. Before
we get to Ben Johnson, they had the AFC
breakfast on Wednesday or excuse me,
Tuesday here at the annual meeting and I
I know there were a lot of discussions
and questions asked to some of the head
coaches about the Bears and Caleb
Williams. I think one of the big ones uh
was Robert Salah of the Tennessee Titans
experiencing him of course in that
December game in San Francisco defending
him. But he said that pairing of Ben
Johnson, Ben's always going to have the
answers to the test of a defense and
then it's up to Caleb to ace that test
in in in critical moments. But I I think
that in his back pocket knowing they can
win games like they did. You're not
always going to, but you're going to be
in a position where you're always going
to have that belief because of the type
of player he is, I think is a is a great
bullet in the gun for the for the Bears
as they move forward. Listen, I don't
think anybody ever comes out of the
locker room more prepared than Ben
Johnson, whether they're ahead or
behind. And everything Robert Salah um
is saying is evidence of what he's seen
out of from his time at Detroit and now
his time with the Chicago Bears. So, I
don't think I've ever grown confidence
in a coach throughout the course of a
season more in my life than uh Ben
Johnson. And I just can't wait to see
what the future holds. But I also can't
wait to see what the future holds for
guys like Caleb and the development of
some of the young guys he's talked about
in his conference of Luther Burton,
Coloulston Lovelin, and you know, all
the other young guys.
>> Score big at your local Chevy dealer.
The Chevy Silverado will take you
through this season in style. Chevy
Drive Chicago, official truck partner of
the Chicago Bears. Let's get to our
conversation with the Bears head coach
here in Arizona. All right. Thank you
for doing this. What did Ben do for Ben
since the season ended? Oh, shoot. It's
It's been uh family time. That that's
really been the the thing that I needed
for my soul was was sinking into the
kids. You know, I got a third grader,
first grader, and you know, we just
potty trained our soon to be
three-year-old. And so, we had a lot of
stuff going on in the household, and so
it was just it's good to sink back into
them. We got math homework. You know,
they're teaching math these days that is
foreign to me. I have no idea how to do
fractions, apparently. So, um that's
been that's been a fun challenge. And
you know, my my first grader just loves
every and every sport. You know, it's
basketball, now we're going on to
baseball, and then um the youngest one
is just she's a handful each and every
day. So that that's really been been
what it's been so far this off
seasonason for me.
>> Good to be dad, though.
>> Good to be dad.
>> Yeah,
>> but half the brains on ball, right?
>> 100%. I'm a little bit behind on father
of the year, so I got I got to catch up
here.
>> Is the fire possibly burning hotter than
it was? Uh, I just talked to Press
Taylor a couple weeks ago. He goes, "The
key word is urgency. Ben is pushing
urgency." So, I'm assuming that fire is
hot.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, I I have felt it. Um,
and I it's been deliberate that, you
know, we get the coaches out of the
building a little bit and now, you know,
back doing the free agency vows and
drafty vows now, some self scout and
they just got off their spring break.
So, I'm looking forward to getting back
in the building and and the urgency that
I'm feeling, I know that they're going
to feel as well. Um, our players are
going to feel it when they come in on
April 20th also. So, I think it's it's
necessary. Um, all the attabo and pats
on the back that everyone's experienced
since the season's ended, those were
great. And yet, we need to understand
that that they're short-lived um if we
don't continue to win.
>> You better tell your playbyplay
announcer the same thing. I can't get
some of it out of my head. Um, yeah. I
mean, the fans are still lit.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And that's the cool thing,
man. We we knew we knew that we have a
fan base that they love their Bears. And
so, it's cool to see the excitement. Um,
and and hopefully our guys use that as
fuel to say, "We got to keep this going.
This is I love this feeling. You know,
we we got to keep this thing going." Um,
and so you do feel some pressure each
and every day to make sure, particularly
when you look at the division, you see
each team in your division get a little
bit better through free agency. And then
we got the draft and they're going to
get better in the draft. So are we. But
you you feel that and I think your
competitive nature comes to the
forefront. You're like, man, I got to
go. Got to go. Got to go. Got to go. I
>> I kind of looked at all the free agents
and I was taken by the fact that these
guys wanted to be here. I I sometimes
you think it's just BS. They wanted to
be here and I think what happened last
season was free advertising for the next
crop of free agents. Would you say
that's fair? Because they they want to
feel what you guys felt.
>> Yeah. Well, I I think anytime you win it
it uh people want to be a part of that
and uh and I think when you are a
winner, your the players on your roster
are more desired by by everyone else as
well. And so, I know we we ended up
having a number of guys sign elsewhere.
Um, and yet we feel really strongly
about the guys we're able to bring into
the into the locker room ourselves to
replace them. And so, um, it's it's an
exciting time. I I know the fact that we
have a a young quarterback that, uh, has
garnered a lot of respect because of
some of these highlight real plays that
he's capable of making, I think that
goes a long way in this day and age. I
know you've said it's only scratching
the surface offensively, but would you
say Caleb
hit some significant mile posts that he
can now build on moving forward in your
scheme?
>> Yeah, I I think he played as poorly as
he's going to play going forward. You
know, I think that's one way to look at
it.
>> That's a very interesting delineation.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I And and he'll tell you
the same thing. He's going to look at
these cutups when he comes back into the
uh into the office and and we're in the
meeting rooms and he's going to be, "Oh
man, we left so much out on the table."
And for us to be what we want to be as a
team and offensively, we got to make
some of these these plays um on a on a
higher basis. And uh and he'll be the
first one to tell you that, you know,
when you complete 58 59% of your throws
um you're leaving something out there.
So it's it's going to take everybody.
It's it's on us as a coaching staff. Um
we we got to do a better job making sure
the primary receiver gets open. Uh our
pass catchers got to do a better job
catching the darn ball. And then Caleb's
going to got to continue to improve in
terms of the decision- making and and
the ball location. And so it's going to
take all of us to be on our mess uh to
get this thing to where we want it to
go. And yet when when you watch it, it's
it's easy to watch a bad cut up and get
discouraged. I see it the other way
though. I I get I get really excited
about it cuz I'm like I know what it
it's going to become. I already know and
uh and our guys got to see it through
that lens and we'll be just fine.
>> I believe this continuity is king. So uh
that goes on both sides of the ball but
around him Keen's backs here coaches
minor changes. How significant is that
for years coming forward here for Caleb?
Yeah, I I think it's a big deal because
he he hasn't had this in a while, you
know, probably since his his Lincoln
Riley days. And so, um, it'll be huge. I
feel great about the quarterback room in
general. Um,
>> you know, you you already mentioned
Tyson and and Case. I think those two
are outstanding for Caleb. Um, as he
continues to grow, not just as a
quarterback, but also as a leader of
this team. You know, a guy like Case
Keenum that's been on so many teams and
has so many experiences of what it
should look like, what it doesn't look
like. Man, I just I think he's an
incredible resource. Um JT Barrett is
going to be better this year coaching
the quarterback position than what he
was a year ago. He's he's a young coach
that's got a really bright future ahead
of him. And the more time he takes on
his craft, he's going to continue to
help help Caleb uh take his game to the
next level as well. Um, and then as an
entire offensive staff, we've got a lot
of continuity. Our guys know what's
important to us, what we need um, uh, to
to have success on game day. And so,
yeah, I feel I feel really strongly
about us taking a step forward. I
>> I read the Dan Pompei wrote a story on
Khalif Fayman. I didn't know half of
what this guy's all about. That story
was amazing. Like this this is a dude.
You know, I think people believe he's a
return specialist, but there is much
more on the bone for him in this
offense.
>> There's no doubt. And uh and of course,
I've got that experience with him. So, I
believe in the person. Um and I
certainly still believe in the player,
too. You know, he he's what, 31 uh this
year and and so he's getting up there a
little bit. And yet, um I know that he
can still take the top off the coverage
if asked. I know that he can run these
choice or option routes underneath and
and be a dangerous run after catch uh
receiver for us and and I know what he
can do in the return game. So, um I'm
I'm really looking forward to what he
does to continue to solidify that
receiver room for Caleb. Um he'll be a
great role model for our young players,
not just in the receiver room, but for
our entire team. The way he goes about
his business is the way we want everyone
to go about their business.
>> And he blocks it. Yeah, it's it's he he
loves the game. He loves the game and uh
you you just can't get enough guys like
that. Um I think it just radiates from
him
>> defensively. The continuity wasn't there
a year ago. Lots of injuries, lots of um
movement there. Um will that be a key
factor like the development of that back
end to marry with the front because you
don't know a lot about some of these
guys?
>> Yeah, I mean it would certainly help. um
you end up missing so many games from
both Jaylen and Kyler. Um
>> Smith didn't play.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Smitty wasn't there. And you
know, I think when you watch the the
clips um over the course of the season,
we we certainly um want to be tighter in
our our coverage, particularly our man
coverage. It was just an area that when
you looked at it, uh we didn't feel like
we gave our pass rush a chance to get
there. and and so it's a a two-edged
sword there where we got to get a little
bit better getting off the ball and
getting after the quarterback, but at
the same time, the longer we can and the
tighter the coverage we can maintain, um
the better off we're going to be there.
So, I'm looking forward to it. We're
still a work in progress on that side of
the ball, uh but I I feel really good
about what we put on tape and being able
to get that better next season.
>> Yeah. and the hits in the draft that you
had, let's uh let's think positively
they'll be the same as a year ago.
Fantastic for the future foundation of
this franchise, Warren.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I I feel feel really good.
I mean, Coloulston, Luther, those two
guys that have been in the building um
as much if not more than anybody else
since the season ended just in terms of
working out and getting their bodies
right. I know they're they're itching to
to get going again. And so, I'm excited
about that. Um, Azy's been in rehab and
Shamar's been in rehabbing. So, I know
those guys really want to get back as
well. So, yeah, we got we got a great
foundation a year ago and and uh you
know, the hope is is for us to be able
to capitalize on that same opportunity
again this year.
>> Is the weight room buzzing?
>> It's it's getting there. It's getting
there. You start to feel it. I think uh
I saw Joe Tuni and Grady Jarrett in last
week. So, when you start getting some of
these old heads back in, that's when
that's when to me you start knowing it's
time. All those guys are starting to
feel the itch now. going there at 5:00
a.m.
>> I might be.
>> All right. Uh, last one. You got a theme
brewing for this year?
>> We're working on that. We're working on
that. So, I still got some time.
>> You do. Thank you.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> Appreciate it.
>> Um, so a lot to pick over there, Tom. I
know you took some notes. Uh, what did
you glean from that uh interview?
>> Well, the thing that I like the most
about it is this is the beginning of
year two. I'm glad after the season was
over, he became a father first and he's
got a wife and young kids and he's got
to stay actively involved in the growth
and the development of their lives. And
so I was super appreciative of that as a
single guy to listen to Ben Johnson to
make sure that plays such an important
role in in himself. But then how
familiar he is with his staff, how
familiar he is with the the the players,
how understanding where Caleb Williams
should be going in his growth and
development in the system. the fact that
he s understands that the weight room is
starting at this time of year to play
the importance and seeing a couple older
guys like Joe Tuni and Grady Jared in
there. So, um you know, I I'm super
encouraged that he has a really good
hand on the big picture of the building
and it's not just micromanaged, it's,
you know, it's managed in a big way.
>> Yeah, he was um he is relaxed, but you
could just see he did a string. I think
he did 12 one-on-one interviews after
that halfhour session. And you know, he
he there's just an intensity about him
that you cannot escape. Every every
person that I've w last night they had
the u the dinner for NFL owners and
everybody's invited who's attending and
you know you talk to people and they
bring up Ben, man, just he is intense.
He is intense. Everybody's
>> you can hear his interviews. Yeah,
>> you can hear it. That's why, you know,
we're we're fortunate enough to ask him
a couple questions at the end of a game.
And that two minutes intimidates me as
much as the three hours that we just
talked about the game. So, and I and
it's it's a it's a respect intimidation.
And that's what even listening to his
interview to start season two with you.
Yeah. And it it definitely h his
intensity is not lost.
>> Yeah. And then his transparency is not
lost on a lot of people either. He is
not shy about saying what's wrong with
the football team on Monday. Not happy
with our staff to get the primary
receiver open. Must do a better job.
Make sure we're doing that. Staying
ahead of the defense. Our scramble tape
was not very good. I I would like to
spend time with him learning about the
scramble tape and the guys hanging on to
the football and whatnot.
>> What? So you got to I I don't know
exactly for verbatim when he said
>> Caleb will never play as worse as he did
last year. something like that to that
effect. And it is true. It just means
that, you know, Caleb's going to be in
the second year of terminology in a
system that he's going to continuously
grow more comfortable and more familiar
with. And like he said, when he went is
going to go back and look at some of
those plays, he's going to say, "Oh my
god, look what I left on the field." And
I I that one little sentence in that
interview was super encouraging to me.
>> So when you when you hear scramble tape,
we all know what that looks like, right?
you're you're you're this is survival
mode and you know get somebody the
football but make the catch. Um how how
how do you make a scramble tape better?
First of all, it's making sure everybody
understands the vulnerability of the
protection called. And if that
vulnerability presents itself, and then
you have to understand that the
quarterback may be under duress and he's
going to be looking for that uh option.
And then you have to make yourself
available to him if you see that uh
quarterback get outside the uh the
tackle box when he's supposed to be in a
straight drop back position. And then I
think you understand what an athlete and
how um you know avoidable
that uh Caleb can be to increase the
likelihood that those scramble uh type
of drills can work. And um but I just
think that comes with familiarity of the
product to every single guy on the
offense, not just the O line or the
quarterback. Tom, what happens because
obviously you've been in in uh football
your whole life and you've experienced
some of what the Bears experienced last
season. Maybe not to the extent the
number of games uh winning like they did
seven times in the final two minutes. Uh
but Ben said, you know, in the last half
of the season, playoffs included, they
scored fewer points in the first three
quarters than the fourth quarter points
combined. And that has to be fixed. Why
are they starting slow? What what do you
get comfort in knowing you still got
things in your hip pocket? You can pull
it out because we got this quarterback
that trusts himself in the fourth
quarter to rally. I mean, how do that
how do you even that out?
>> You know, I think experience on time
together, playing together, making sure
that cuz Ben changes the game plan uh uh
in such a big way from week in and week
out. You're just not running uh a
hamster on a wheel that running the same
game plan that you ran last week. This
is new plays that are all inserted for
the first time against your next
opponent. And so I think when that
terminology becomes second nature where
Caleb can make certain adjustments to
the play he called the different
relationships he grows with receivers or
the running back start to get an
understanding of how to anticipate where
the hole is probably going to open up
before it's ever blocked. All those
little things that everybody has to
learn, not just Caleb.
>> Hey Bears fans. Steinhoff a proud
partner of the Chicago Bears this Bears
season. Steinhoffles is partnering with
Special Spaces Illinois to create dream
bedrooms for children battling cancer.
For every false start caused by the
Bears defense during a home game,
Steinhoffles will donate $1,000 to
Special Spaces Illinois. Shop in store
and online at steinhoffles.com. Let's
talk defense. He's spending a ton of
time, which he didn't do last year uh
because of the be beginning of of
starting something new uh in the
defensive meeting rooms. He says he's
learning a lot about football. Helps him
as an offensive coordinator as well. But
uh that need to u manage the entire team
is what your job as a head coach is. Uh
how significant is that for him?
>> I think it's huge and one specific thing
he brought up in your conversation is he
wants to play man-to-man defense better.
And I do think that's one element that
you can really offer the guys up front.
If you can go back there and play man
defense better, then you can blitz from
a lot of different directions. You can
overload sides. you can have faith in
the type of defensive back play you have
in order to be uh offer a variety of
plans up front. So something that small
part not it's a major part of the
defense but with the one element of it
is man defense according to Ben if you
can get your football team to play that
better then you're talking about Dennis
Allen being able to be more creative up
front in offering a lot of unsuspected
pressures that your opponent may not be
prepared for. Tom, like we spoke last
week in the podcast or maybe it was on
Bears Weekly that you know what they did
in free agency, you and I felt it was
thumbs up. They didn't go crazy with the
cash. They didn't focus on just one
bigname free agent. They got a lot
deeper uh on the defensive side of the
ball, which they needed to. uh they they
filled some holes that now they can go
into the draft and feel comfortable in
drafting any position sticking true to
your board, take the best player
available and move forward. Uh I don't
think any of that's a bunch of cliches.
I think that's exactly where they're
poised to attack and if they get a draft
like they did a year ago, that is going
to mean big things for the Bears now and
in the near future, two, three, four
years down the road.
>> Yeah. you know, after free agents, I
don't believe there's any position is
closed where you you know, you can you
still have the ability and the
opportunity to look at every single
position out there. Yeah, you made your
left tackle position more competitive.
You brought in a day one starter at the
center position that you needed. You
brought in a linebacker who's going to
be given a starting jersey the day he
gets here, just like the safety
position. But when you look at the
amount of talent there is in the
defensive side of the ball in
preparation for this draft, you can go
out there and you can double up a
position and you know bring in those
types of numbers that keep that
possession competitive and then you can
make some decisions about the future in
the future. So I still think every
option is open. Um, and um, you know,
we'll we'll see where this thing ends up
going. Even, you know, and I'm not and
even with Coulson and Cole, I'm not
saying the tight end position is closed
because we see how creative Ben is with
the three tight end um, in the variety
of positions they're expected to play.
So, I I'm super excited about this draft
and I know they're picking 25, but you
just don't know what's going to happen.
Tom, if if none of those players that
are rehabbing right now, from Dia Dengbo
to Shamar Turner, uh to TJ Edwards, uh
to
I guess you could put Grady Jared in
that mode as well, would how would you
feel if they were not coming off injury?
How how would you look at the defense in
particular as you move into the draft
phase here? Yeah, I I would be really
excited because I think they in I think
they increase their speed and their
physicality with uh Kobe Bryant and
Devin Bush. I think when you look at the
other guys that you mentioned up front
that if they come in healthy and
competitive, I think it increases the
competition on a daily practice basis
that really makes it better. And then I
think Dennis Allen gets a better
understanding of what his capabilities
are playing defense. at the last game of
the year when we're watching him play
seven defensive backs. Maybe that
changes now because you do have a little
bit more speed at linebacker, but you
know, I don't know where Noah Su is
going to be. I don't know where TJ's
going to be, but so you still have
positions that we need to learn more
about September, not at the end of
March.
>> I think the competition's going to be
intense. I think they're they're loaded
up at positions. Tech, you know, Nephi
Su is on board the Bears uh at the
linebacker position. Noah's brother who
is uh of course rehabbing his injury.
So, you know, you've got you've got a
lot of competition. Terrell Smith coming
back at corner. Uh he'll be competing
with Tyreek Stevenson for that other
starting job, barring any other
additions in the draft. And uh I just
think there's going to be competition
across the board. That's what Ben
thrives in. He loves seeing that. He
wants that.
>> You know what one I do? I will say one
thing. So, you're a new head coach,
you're a new defensive coordinator,
you're a a a special teams coordinator
that's been around a little bit and the
co new head coaches and the new coaches
on staff, you kind of have to learn a
little bit about the personalities of
the players you're coaching. How
challengeable are they? And that's one
thing about Dennis Allen, defensive
coordinator, Ben Johnson, and all the
other coaches. They know a little bit
more about their talent, and they know
how to turn that button up a higher.
They know how they can coach a guy on a
day-to-day basis, and I think that helps
the coaches as well.
>> How do you tell a cashier you're a Bears
fan without telling them you're a Bears
fan? With a Chicago Bears PNC Bank Visa
debit card, which gets you exclusive
discounts on Bears merchandise. Find out
more at pnc.com/bearscard.
So, on Wednesday, uh we'll have some of
that for you in our Bears weekly show,
one-on-one interviews with the chairman,
George Halis McCasky, and president and
CEO Kevin Warren. I'm sure stadium talk
will be uh among the many topics that
will be discussed as we uh hopefully get
closer to a decision on that front. And
uh what are your thoughts on the backing
of the NFL? And we we assumed this would
be one day, but it's coming sooner
rather than later. Having professional
flag football, men's and women's teams
with the backing of a lot of um of
financial input from outside
organizations and um also backing of a
lot of former NFL players that are
putting their names to this thing.
>> Listen, man, I think it's a awesome. I
think anytime you put more people on
their feet participating in a sport,
it's better for them and better for the
people that maybe thought they never had
a chance of playing a competitive sport.
I have a friend of mine and she writes
for the college newspaper at the
University of Georgia and she just wrote
this article about the fastest growing
sport in Georgia is women's flag
football. And I appreciate the fact that
there's more offerings to more pe people
to play sports. I watch u the women's
NCAA bracket and wa and follow Notre
Dame until they get got beat and stuff.
So I I like it, man. I'm all for it. I
love the fact that Jeffiac could have
came out in eighth grade and played
sport played football.
>> Exactly. Every sip of Blue Moon's
Belgian style wheat ale crafted with
Valencia orange peel and coriander is a
winning drive for your taste buds. Kick
off your game day with Blue Moon. That's
going to wrap this up. Join us on Bears
Weekly on Thursday night 6:00 on ESPN
1000. Thanks to head coach Ben Johnson
for Tom there. I'm Jeff Jonia. Thanks
for listening everybody. Please
subscribe down Chicago Bears official
app, Apple, Spotify, YouTube or wherever
you get your podcast. Bear down
everybody.